No!
Oh, there you are!
Jougo!
Looks like most of your body's back.
Yeah, this place is relaxing.
Humans don't come anywhere near it.
Lacking a body really is a problem.
It makes self-preservation so inefficient.
Mahito, you're awfully worn down yourself.
Oh, you could tell?
Sukuna and his vessel
are my natural enemies.
I started this game because
I happened to acquire a new toy,
but it just didn't go so well.
It was great at first, though.
Are you sure I shouldn't have just
used a hostage to force him into a pact?
Like, "Hand your body over to Sukuna
if you don't want to see him killed."
No, pacts are only placed
by oneself on oneself.
It's not easy to forge pacts with others,
or due to intervention from others.
Maybe I should have just given that thing
a lethal wound instead of transfiguring it.
Then Sukuna might have been able to heal
it with his reverse cursed technique.
Know your place, fool.
No, not with that personality.
I think he would have refused either way.
Jougo...
Touching Sukuna made me realize that
we should probably proceed
with Getou's plan for now.
Sukuna is that valuable.
Gather all the fingers and
offer them to Sukuna, huh?
Even if we're all wiped out in the process, eh?
Very well.
I don't need to be the one laughing
in the wasteland a century from now.
As long as curses stand there as
people, that's all that matters.
Oh, you get it!
Then first, let's go retrieve the
six fingers Jujutsu Tech has.
Is that necessary?
The sorcerers are only
keeping Itadori Yuuji around
so he can take in Sukuna's fingers, right?
He'll still eat them, even if we leave them be.
The higher-ups at Jujutsu Tech
are struggling to measure
Itadori Yuuji's strength as a vessel,
to see how many he can take
before he goes berserk.
They won't let him take them in
until they've gathered all the fingers...
With just one exception.
Exception
I want to feed them to him right away!
And we can't wait that long, right?
Worst case, there's also a chance
they'll eliminate Itadori Yuuji.
Into the tiger's den, huh?
Well, what should we do, then?
I've already taken steps.
That's why I allowed Jujutsu Tech
to retrieve the fingers we had.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Episode 14: Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event - Group Battle 0 -
Nanami, talk about something interesting.
Okay, I've got it!
Let's play catch with discarded rice balls
while discussing the separation of church and state!
Let's post a video of it and troll people.
Enjoy that on your own.
What kind of idea is that?
Drinking game time! Name things
you love about Gojou Satoru!
Everything!
Please keep that attitude going.
Itadori-kun needs that
kind of idiocy right now.
You'll take on and complete
several harder missions.
That wasn't what I meant by "harder," though.
Nanami, does Yuuji know about
that finger in Yoshino's—
I haven't told him.
Knowing him, he'd just feel
unnecessarily responsible.
I'm glad I left you in charge.
And the finger?
I submitted it to the higher-ups, of course.
If I gave it to you, you'd just
feed it to Itadori-kun, right?
Tsk.
But is it really okay to bring him back?
If the fact that he's alive becomes
known at the exchange event,
won't the higher-ups just target him again?
Even if they do, Yuuji will be just fine now.
You know that better than anyone, don't you?
Sensei!
Oh, Nanamin's here, too.
Well, c'mon!
Let's hurry up and go see everyone!
So excited!
"I thought you were dead..."
Touching Reunion
With Friends
So excited!
"Nice to meet you!!"
Deciding Factor of His First Impression,
First Meeting With the Second Years
So excited!
Kyoto Students Appear!!
Exchange Event Begins!
"Beginner's Guide to
the Exchange Event"
So excited!
Yuuji, are you planning to just show up
like normal after dragging it out this long?
Huh? I can't?!
Even among sorcerers,
you rarely see someone say they've actually
been alive two whole months after they died.
We have to make it a surprise!
A surprise?
Just leave it to me.
The first-years will be laughing
and crying from happiness and shock.
I'm so glad!
You're alive!
The second-years and Kyoto
students will cry with them.
Thank goodness! Thank goodness!
And someone among them
will choke up and vomit,
Blegh!
and in the end, it'll even solve global warming!
Cool!
Sweet!
What do I do?!
Sensei, what should I do?!
You don't have to do anything!
Just do exactly as I say,
and go with the flow!
So what should I do?!
Just go with the flow!
It'll be enough of a surprise
just to see he's alive.
Kyoto
Come have fun in Kyoto
The Complete Guide
What?!
Why are you all empty-handed?!
What are you doing with all that luggage?
What do you mean?
We're going to Kyoto, right?
Fortunes
For the exchange event
with our sister school in Kyoto?
It's an exchange event with
our sister school in Kyoto.
Held in Tokyo.
Ueno Specialty
Panda
No way!
What did I make all those
preparations for, then?!
No wonder our conversations
have been a bit off lately.
Yeah.
I was totally ready to go sightseeing!
Salmon.
It's held at the school that
won in the previous year.
This sucks! What a scam!
Then don't go winning, you idiots!
We weren't in it last year!
Only Yuuta participated to
make the numbers match up!
That was prior to freeing Rika.
Apparently, it was an overwhelming win.
I didn't see it, though,
since it was held in Kyoto.
I won't forgive you, Okkotsu Yuuta!
Not that I've ever even met you!
That's misdirected anger.
Salmon.
Hey.
They're here.
Oh, look. It's everyone from Tokyo together.
You went out of your way to greet us?
Disgusting.
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Second-Year
Zenin Mai
Okkotsu's not here.
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Third-Year
Toudou Aoi
Shut up. Hurry up and hand over the cake box,
and the yatsuhashi, kudzu noodles,
and buckwheat cookies.
Salmon.
You guys hungry?
Who is that first-year?
She's scary.
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Third-Year
Nishimiya Momo
Never mind Okkotsu being absent.
Isn't having two first-years a major handicap?
A robot! It's a robot!
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Second-Year
Ultimate Mechamaru
Age is irrelevant to jujutsu sorcerers.
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Third-Year
Kamo Noritoshi
Especially with Fushiguro-kun.
He's from the Zenin bloodline,
but he's more talented
than the head of the clan.
Tsk.
Something to say?
Nope.
Now, now...
Please calm down, you two.
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Second-Year
Miwa Kasumi
Okay, now.
Let's not fight amongst ourselves.
My goodness, these children.
Jujutsu Tech, Semi-First-Grade Sorcerer
Kyoto School Leader
Iori Utahime
So, where's that idiot?
Satoru's late.
As if that idiot would ever show up on time.
No one said "idiot" referred to Gojou-sensei.
Sorry for the wait!
Tsk. Gojou Satoru.
Gojou Satoru!
Hey, I see everyone's together.
I was on a business trip overseas.
So I will now hand out souvenirs!
This is sudden.
Sure it's not jet lag?
Okay, everyone from Kyoto gets this
protective charm from a particular tribe.
None for you, Utahime.
I don't need one!
And for everyone from Tokyo, we have this!
Overly excited adults are creepy.
Hey! OPP!
It's your departed friend,
Itadori Yuuji-kun!
Huh?!
Huh? Huh?!
They don't seem happy at all!
N-No way.
Okay, everyone from Kyoto!
This is Sukuna's vessel, Itadori Yuuji-kun!
Wh-What about the ones from Kyoto?
They're too absorbed in their souvenirs!
Sukuna's vessel?!
What's the meaning of this?
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto School Principal
Gakuganji Yoshinobu
Principal Gakuganji!
Oh, thank goodness.
I was worried you might
just die from the shock.
You damn brat!
Hey.
Uh, yes?
You got something to say?
Huh?
I'm sorry for keeping quiet
about being alive.
Itadori Rejoins
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Jujutsu Technical High School
Tokyo-Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event
The Tokyo-Kyoto Sister School
Exchange Event will be held over two days.
The first day is a group battle...
Wacky
Cursed Spirit Exorcism Race
The Wacky Cursed Spirit Exorcism Race!
The rules are simple.
Second-Grade
The first team to exorcise
the second-grade cursed spirit
released in the designated area wins.
Several third-grade and lower cursed spirits
will be released into the designated area, as well.
If a winner is not decided by sundown,
the team that exorcises the most wins.
There are absolutely no other rules.
Of course, you're welcome
to sabotage the others,
but remember, you're all on the same
side in the fight against the curses.
This exchange event will allow
you to learn about yourselves
and your comrades through competition.
Be certain not to kill other competitors
or injure them beyond recovery.
That's it.
You're all dismissed until the
event commences at noon!
\hTokyo Side Meeting\h
Excuse me...
Depending on how you look at it,
this could be considered
very extreme bullying.
Shut up and stay that way for a while.
Now, now...
You heard his explanation.
Cut him some slack.
The panda talked!
Salmon, salmon.
What?
Inumaki-senpai is a cursed speech user.
Cursed speech is a technique that amplifies
the power and compulsion of words.
He limits his vocabulary to keep others safe.
So if he told someone to
go die, they'd actually die?
That's really powerful.
It's nothing that convenient.
It's all case by case, depending
on their difference in strength.
If he uses powerful words,
he's hit with massive feedback.
Worst case, it could affect him.
Limiting his vocabulary is a way
for Toge to protect himself, as well.
So how are you able to speak, Senpai?
Are you some new breed of panda?
Blabbing on about people's techniques...
It's fine.
Toge's isn't that kind of technique, anyway.
More importantly, Yuuji...
Give me back Slaughter Demon.
You borrowed it from Satoru, right?
Gimme!
Here you go!
I broke it.
It's not coming back!
Gojou-sensei... has it...
Tsk, that blindfolded dumbass!
Gross.
So, what's the plan?
The group battle format
is what we expected,
but we have another member now.
Do we change strategies?
There's not much time.
Bonito flakes.
Well, that depends on Yuuji.
What can you do?
Punch, kick...
We have enough of that.
Huh?
I don't know what he's been
doing since he's been dead,
but if everyone from Tokyo and Kyoto
fought him at once without cursed energy,
Itadori would win.
Oh?
Megumi's saying that after fighting Toudou?
That makes it convincing.
Interesting.
\hKyoto Side Meeting\h
Kill Sukuna's vessel, Itadori Yuuji.
He is not a person.
So it will go unquestioned.
It'll be treated as an accident.
There's no need to hold back or hesitate.
I don't want to...
You say to kill him,
but he's here because he didn't die, right?
I've heard that Itadori's
previous death was suicide.
What is the one thing you must be cautious
about when ending a hostile sorcerer?
Kamo.
Yes.
You must kill them with cursed
energy to prevent them from
coming back as a curse after death.
Exactly.
If another delivers the finishing blow
with cursed energy, then all is well.
At present, Itadori Yuuji
has control of the body.
Unless Sukuna comes out,
he's just a first-year.
Killing him will be—
This is stupid. Do what you want.
Come back, Toudou.
The principal isn't finished yet.
Takada-chan's making a guest
appearance on a walking show at 11.
Do I need to explain any more?
You can record it. Come back here.
I'm going to watch the recording
and watch it in real time!
Who do you take me for?
That's your problem here?!
Listen, all of you.
You listen, too, old man.
I've long been disappointed in you all
and your bad taste in women.
Plot and scheme all you want on your own.
But if you try to order me around again,
I'll kill you.
What do we do now?
I don't think we'll be able to carry
out the plan with him like that.
The principal's gone off somewhere, too.
I don't want to be killed by that guy.
Does it even matter?
He's going to go straight
for the Tokyo team, anyway.
If he's just going to go berserk,
we can focus on the game.
But we have to kill Itadori Yuuji, right?
We're seriously doing this?
I don't think he'll go as far as killing him.
Though he probably could.
Then we'll need someone to
keep an eye on Toudou
and deliver the final blow to Itadori Yuuji.
I don't like this.
We'll have cursed spirits to deal with, too,
so we'll be in two-man cells anyway.
That works out for us.
No.
Allowing a half-wit like Itadori Yuuji
to be a sorcerer at Jujutsu Tech
is a serious problem.
One that goes beyond this exchange event.
I cannot overlook this as the
eldest son of the Kamo clan.
We're all attacking Itadori Yuuji together.
Hold on.
What happens if Inumaki-kun
is with Itadori-kun?
Having all of us in one place is a risky
move with that cursed speech user.
Worst case, he could
wipe us all out at once.
That's true.
No, if you know he's coming,
he's not that scary to face.
Let me have Maki.
That brown-haired first-year, too, if possible.
You're sounding just like Toudou.
So what did you want?
Huh? Why are you mad?
I'm not mad, actually.
Right? I haven't done anything, after all.
There's someone working with either
a curse user or curses at Jujutsu Tech.
Impossible!
A curse user might be one thing,
but working with curses?
A lot of them on that level
have been popping up lately.
They understand human speech, and they've
formed a faction that's operating with purpose.
They might think they're just
working with a curse user, but...
I'd like to ask you to handle
investigating those at Kyoto, Utahime.
What would you do if I was the traitor?
No way.
You're weak, and you don't have the guts—
Scary! Hysterics won't win men, you know.
I! Am! The senior here!
Itadori.
You okay?
Yeah, sounds like I've got
a big role, but I'll manage.
I'm not talking about that.
Something happened, right?
Huh? Nothing happened.
Okay, it did.
But it's true that I'm fine.
In fact, because of what happened,
I don't want to lose to anyone.
Okay, then.
I don't really want to lose, either.
What do you mean, "really"?
You already got sent rolling around once!
Overwhelm them!
Let's thoroughly trounce them!
For Maki-san's sake, too!
Don't say stuff like that.
Pollack roe.
Yeah! For Maki-san's sake, too!
Don't say stuff like that.
Well, in that case,
let's win!
What are you doing taking the lead?
Ow!
Juju Stroll
Sushi Eishuu
Hello! Today we're here at the
long-standing sushi shop, Eishuu!
You should do that kind of thing, too.
You'd be mad at me if I did.
Welcome.
What do you like, Takada-chan?
Goatfish! And room temperature sake!
They're great together!
How old are you again?
Huh?
How long have you been making sushi, boss?
I've been doing it since I was 20.
Which means... about 300 years?
Are you drunk?
Here's the goatfish you ordered.
Mm, it's so good!
Can I have yours, too?
Of course not.
Sorry!
Honestly, what are you thinking?
Well, it just looked so delicious!
She's drunk.
Tan, Taka-tan!
That's my Takada-chan.
Sensei, did you know "OPP"
actually stands for something?
Huh? It does?
Ocean Pacific Peace.
Seriously?
Episode 15:
Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event - Group Battle 1 -